thespectrum.net 2012-12-30

# SPECTRUM NEXUS · Privacy Policy

You can feel confident about how we use the information you give us. We will not disclose your information to any third parties. We will only use your information to help us provide services to you. By using Spectrum Nexus' web site you accept our policy. 

**Do I have to give Spectrum Nexus personal information?**  
The only instances you will be asked to submit personal information is if you're sending us an e-mail through our contact form, if you join the [message forums](http://www.animesymposium.com/forum/), if you sign up for the free giveaway/newsletter, or if you sign up for our free e-mail service.

Our newsletter is a service provided by [FeedBlitz](http://www.feedblitz.com/privacy.asp). They are a reputable company that provides free newsletter services to thousands of websites. By signing up for our newsletter you are accepting [FeedBlitz's Privacy Policy](http://www.feedblitz.com/privacy.asp).

Our free [e-mail service](http://fusiongt.mail.everyone.net/email/scripts/joinuser.pl) is provided to us by [Everyone.net](http://www.everyone.net/). They are a reputable company that provides free e-mail service to large businesses as well as colleges. We do not receive personal information when users sign up for this e-mail service; we are only allowed to view user names (and not passwords). By signing up for this free e-mail service you are accepting [Everyone.net's Privacy Policy](http://www.everyone.net/email-company/p_policy.html). 

**What does Spectrum Nexus do with my information?**  
If you submit an e-mail to us through our contact form we will only use that information to send you a reply to your inquiry. If you sign up for the [message forum](http://www.animesymposium.com/forum/) we will never use your personal information in a harmful way; nor will we share it with any third parties. Our free giveaway requires users to sign up for a newsletter, and we will send our newsletter to the email you provide. If you win the giveaway, we will require a name and address for us to ship the giveaway to you. 

**What about advertisements on Spectrum Nexus?**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**What about Spectrum Nexus' server logs, user rating scripts, and polls?**  
The only information that is stored is your IP address. This information will not be used in any other way beside providing us with information such as if the user submitted a score through the user rating script they will not be permitted again to submit it until after a certain amount of days. The same goes with server logs and polls; IP addresses are simply used to enable our "user submitted information" to be more accurate (to discourage malicious use of our system). 

**Links to other websites**  
We only link to websites that we feel will benefit the user. 

**Who should I contact?**  
If you have any concerns about the information we hold about you, or the way we use it, please use our contact form to send an e-mail to Spectrum Nexus.
